{
    "id": "a7026eae70c14751b5b56f9504e98646",
    "title": "Conjunctive Adverbs Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "Vegetables are rich sources of vitamins and antioxidants and ……………… eating vegetables is essential for good health.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "since",
                "as",
                "hence"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "19d4aacb0c1c461ab1f2932c60f82841"
        },
        {
            "question": "‘The last bus has gone.’ ‘………………….., we are going to have to walk.’",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Therefore",
                "As",
                "Then"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "4c4b34e6927b4b958264bdedb9544885"
        },
        {
            "question": "………………… the starter, I thought the meal was nice.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Apart from",
                "Besides",
                "In addition"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "c75d95e5b305445eb03eafdc726b7a76"
        },
        {
            "question": "I bought that car. It looked good and, ………………….., it was reasonably priced.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "besides",
                "moreover"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "c25875f6998843d58301c55293c41b4f"
        },
        {
            "question": "Studies seem to suggest that bright blue and bright yellow are the most visible and ………………….. the safest colors for vehicles.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "therefore",
                "also"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "46ee61bd0b3148d98761cbc2a835a10a"
        },
        {
            "question": "You had better mend your ways ………………….., you will land in serious trouble.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "hence",
                "otherwise"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "1c89a53196154d27b9afcbcf7774ced2"
        },
        {
            "question": "She didn’t leave her husband ………………….. the fact that he had cheated on her.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "however",
                "although",
                "despite"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "0ae0ecc7a9c548109d30df77d0f216b1"
        },
        {
            "question": "………………….. each individual is unique in many ways, members of the same species share many common characteristics.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Despite",
                "Although",
                "However"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "f0796ad5815c4220b8117ba355267cd2"
        },
        {
            "question": "They have recruited more people and …………………. the service has improved",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "as result",
                "as consequence",
                "consequently"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "795f44cf9f0b4589b66823b609045bb5"
        },
        {
            "question": "I was not confident of winning. …………………, I decided to give it a try.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "So",
                "Nevertheless",
                "Although"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "d81552b6a5394ab9b05ff50d987fb259"
        }
    ]
}